all right it's Tuesday September 13th
u redu je u utorak 13. septembra
2016 and hear the stories were covering
2016 i čuti priče koje su pokrivale
this week the operators of the video s d
ovog tjedna operatori videa sd
das for hire service have been arrested
Das za najam su uhapšeni
google is offering uber competitor
google nudi uber konkurenta
pricing on maps the samsung galaxy note
cijena na kartama samsung galaxy note
7 has been recalled because it might
7 je povučeno jer je moglo
catch on fire a robot has been used to
na vatru je navikao robot
operate in a man's eye with perfect
djeluju u čovjekovom oku sa savršenim
results and weaponized drones are now
rezultati i oružane dronove su sada
legal in North Dakota these stories are
pravni u North Dakota ove priče su
coming right up don't go anywhere Jeff
stiće ne idu nigdje Jeff
Weston Yemen you're building a brand new
Weston Jemen gradite potpuno novi
beautiful website what are you but
prekrasna web stranica što si ti ali
you're terrible actor what this we're
ti si strašan glumac šta smo mi
acting comes into play I don't know
gluma stupa u igru ​​ne znam
where I think you're supposed to act
gde mislim da bi trebalo da postupite
okay I'm building a really cool website
U redu, ja pravim stvarno cool sajt
are you building a really cool website
gradite stvarno cool web stranicu
you need hosting one of the things about
trebate ugostiti jednu od stvari
a hosting account is you don't want to
hosting račun je da ne želite
have limitations put on your website
imate ograničenja stavljena na vašu web lokaciju
let's sure how much hard drive space do
da budemo sigurni koliko prostora na tvrdom disku ima
you have how many email accounts how
imate koliko računa e-pošte
many domains can point to it well we've
mnogi domeni mogu pokazati na to dobro
got an amazing deal for you for a very
za tebe je dobio neverovatan posao
limited time cat five dot TV / dreamhost
ograničeno vrijeme mačka pet dot TV / dreamhost
for just five dollars and a bit of
za samo pet dolara i malo
change per month you are going to get
Mesečna promena ćete dobiti
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
neograničen hosting web stranica neograničen
email accounts on that hosting service
račune e-pošte na toj usluzi hostinga
you are also going to receive a free
takođe ćete dobiti besplatno
domain name the roots are your own com
ime domena korijeni su vaš vlastiti com
dice to put that amazing website that
kockice da stavite tu neverovatnu stranicu
you've been working on on there if you
radili ste na tome ako ste vi
run if you want to build a wordpress
trčite ako želite da napravite wordpress
site fine sign up cat5 TV / dreamhost
site fine sign up cat5 TV / dreamhost
just don't put out of the papers are
samo ne stavljajte papire
just don't do it but hey it's a great
samo nemoj to raditi, ali hej to je sjajno
deal folks best deal you're going to
najbolje je da se dogovorite
find five dollars and change per month
nađite pet dolara i promijenite mjesečno
go to cap five dot TV / dreamhost i'm
idite na pet tačaka TV / dreamhost ja sam
jeff weston and hear the top stories
Jeff Weston i čuju priče
from the category 5 TV news room one of
iz kategorije 5 TV vijesti jedna od
the more popular cyberattack peddlers
popularniji prodavači cyber-napada
just came crashing down
samo se srušio
Israeli law enforcement has arrested yar
Izraelska policija je uhapsila yar
diba Danny and hit a hurry as part of an
diba Danny i žuri se kao dio jednog
FBI investigation into their alleged
FBI istraga o njihovim navodnim
control of videos one of the most
kontrola video snimaka je jedna od najvažnijih
popular paid attack platforms according
po popularnim plaćenim napadnim platformama
to information unearthed by security
na informacije otkrivene bezbednošću
guru Brian Krebs from a third-party hack
guru Brian Krebs iz treće strane
targeting vetoes the teens two teens
ciljanje veta na tinejdžerke
raked in nearly six or at least six
rakiran u skoro šest ili najmanje šest
hundred eighteen thousand dollars
sto osamnaest hiljada dolara
launching a majority of the distributed
pokretanje većine distribuiranih
denial-of-service campaigns that you've
kampanje poricanja servisa koje imate
been hearing about recent years the
je slušao o poslednjim godinama
platform itself is also offline although
sama platforma je van mreže iako
that's due to one of the video is
to je zbog jednog od video snimaka
victim's back connect security using a
žrtve se povezuju sa bezbednošću pomoću a
bogus internet address claim to stem the
lažne internet adrese tvrde da su se zaustavile
flood of traffic hitting its servers
poplava saobraćaja je pogodila svoje servere
badani and hurry weren't exactly careful
badani i žurba nisu bili baš oprezni
though about covering their tracks creb
iako o prikrivaju tragove creb
says the pair hosted videos on a server
kaže da je par hostovao video na serveru
connected to hurry and it's email and
povezan sa žurbom i to je email i
SMS notifications pointed to the two
SMS obaveštenja ukazuju na dva
they even wrote a technical paper on the
čak su napisali i tehnički dokument o
DDoS attacks while bananas old facebook
DDoS napada dok banane stare facebook
page references the Apple Jacks Outen is
stranica upućuje na Apple Jacks Outen
a pseudonym that's Apple J for ck he
pseudonim je Apple J za ck he
used to conduct vidos business and if
koristi se za obavljanje poslova vida i ako
that weren't enough vitas refused to
to nije bilo dovoljno vitasa odbilo
target any israeli site since its owners
ciljaju svaki izraelski sajt od njegovih vlasnika
since it was the owners home country
budući da je to bio vlasnik zemlje
both suspects are out on bail although
oba osumnjičena su na slobodi iako
they won't have much freedom officials
oni neće imati mnogo zvaničnika slobode
have placed them under house arrest for
za koje su ih stavili u kućni pritvor
ten days confiscated their passports and
Deset dana su im oduzeli pasoše i
bar them from using any telecom devices
zabranite im da koriste telekomunikacione uređaje
for 30 days it's unclear if they face
30 dana nije jasno da li se suočavaju
extradition to the US now the bust isn't
izručenje u SAD sada nije
going to stop paid denial of service
će prestati plaćati uskraćivanje usluge
attacks hesby danny and hurry
napada hesby Danny i žuri
demonstrated it doesn't take much more
pokazalo je da ne treba mnogo više
than a botnet and some basic business
nego botnet i neke osnovne poslove
savvy to get started however it may put
razboritost da bi se počelo kako god bilo
a temporary dent in the volume of those
privremeni otisak u obimu tih
attacks and it'll certainly spook videos
napada i sigurno će zaprepastiti video zapise
competitors who have been careless about
takmičari koji su bili neoprezni
hiding their activities Wow yeah you
skrivajući svoje aktivnosti Wow yeah you
know I the question sometimes comes up
znam da se ponekad nameće pitanje
Jeff why do hackers do this why do
Jeff, zašto to rade hakeri
hackers attack website six hundred and
hakeri napadaju web stranice šest stotina i
eighteen thousand plus dollars as well
i osamnaest hiljada plus dolara
as well
kao dobro
that's why they do it can you imagine
zato oni to mogu da zamislite
being a teenager and splitting that two
biti tinejdžer i dijeliti to dvoje
ways that would buy you a few boxes of
načinima koji bi vam kupili nekoliko kutija
kraft dinner maybe driving a nice little
kraft večera možda vožnja lijepo malo
sports car I'll tell you that much yep
sportski auto Reći ću vam toliko
that's why yep that's why Wow all right
zato je tako Wow dobro
google has announced Thursday that it's
Google je u četvrtak objavio da je
adding a new ride hailing partners to
dodavanje nove vožnje u kojoj su partneri
maps uber was already integrated into
mape uber su već integrisane
Maps now users will also be able to see
Karte koje će sada korisnici moći da vide
price estimates for lift and some more
procjene cijena za lift i još neke
region specific options such as get in
specifične opcije u regionu kao što su ulazak
New York City all without leaving the
New York City sve bez napuštanja
Maps app basically Google just created
Aplikacija Mape u osnovi je upravo napravila Google
the first-ever ride-hailing price
prva cijena za vožnju
comparison tool now ubers partnership
alata za poređenje sada partnerstvo
with Google is different from their API
sa Google-om se razlikuje od njihovog API-ja
which has seen sites like Harvard
koja je videla lokacije kao što je Harvard
startup urban hail blocked for offering
startup urbana gradska blokada za ponudu
competitive pricing now with Google
konkurentne cijene sada s Googleom
however it is a direct integration and
međutim, to je direktna integracija i
doesn't use ubers API so it's not a
ne koristi ubers API, tako da nije
violation of the terms of use google has
kršenje uvjeta korištenja google ima
partnered with other ride-hailing
udružio se s drugim vožnjama
services through maps before Loula in
usluge putem mapa prije Loula u
India and 99 taxis in Brazil among
Indija i 99 taksija u Brazilu
others this is the first time it's
drugi ovo je prvi put
adding direct competitors to uber in the
dodavanje direktnih konkurenata uber u
US though so why uber was willing to
SAD, pa zašto je uber bio voljan
work with Google to build a price
rad sa Google-om na izgradnji cijene
comparison tool while simultaneously
alata za usporedbu istovremeno
blocking startups like urban hail well
blokiranje startupa poput urbanog grada
the most likely reason is because uber
najvjerovatniji razlog je uber
needs Google Google Maps has hundreds of
Google Google Maps ima stotine
millions of users so that means more
milioni korisnika, što znači više
exposure and more riders for uber now
izloženost i više jahača za sada
the price comparison aspect is just an
aspekt poređenja cena je samo
unfortunate side effect that uber is
nesretni sporedni efekat koji je uber
really going to have to accept or risk
zaista će morati prihvatiti ili riskirati
losing that exposure I've never used
izgubio sam izloženost koju nikada nisam koristio
uber but for anybody who does they
ali za svakoga ko to radi
either love it or they hate it and every
ili ga vole ili ih mrze i svaki
time I turn on the news there seems to
kada uključim vesti
be some sort of competition or anti boob
biti neka vrsta konkurencije ili anti boob
or something sure yeah why not taking a
ili nešto sigurno da, zašto ne uzimati
bit of a beating as far as having a
malo premlaćivanja što se tiče a
corner on the market but that's tech now
kutak na tržištu, ali to je sada tehnologija
adays everything moves so fast good
sve se pokreće tako brzo
though the Google is able to get around
iako je Google u mogućnosti da zaobiđe
the API Absalom
API Absalom
terms of use because of the fact that
uslove korišćenja zbog činjenice da
the otherwise you end up falling into
inače ćete završiti
this monopolist situation yep really
ova monopolistička situacija je zaista
that's what it comes down to makes you
to se svodi na vas
wonder though if as these things happen
pitam se da li se ove stvari događaju
people are going to get smarter with
ljudi će biti pametniji
their contracts to try and block this
njihove ugovore da pokušaju blokirati ovo
kind of stuff so that like Google
takve stvari, tako da poput Google-a
couldn't do that but like you said
to ne mogu, ali kao što si rekao
though would you would you discard
ali da li biste odbacili
Google's Google's promoting your service
Googleov Google promovira vašu uslugu
yeah it come on like when you go on to
Da, to se dešava kao kad nastavite
google to search for cab and you click
google da traži kabinu i klikneš
on it and boom you just pull the first
na njemu i bum samo povučeš prvu
one at the best price don't you want to
jedan po najboljoj cijeni ne želite
be that absolutely yeah yeah I wouldn't
da apsolutno da da, ne bih
want to throw it away do definitely not
Želim da ga baci učiniti definitivno ne
all right airline passengers have been
svi pravi avio-putnici su bili
warned by us authorities not to switch
Upozorili smo nas vlasti da ne mijenjamo
on or charge the Samsung Galaxy Note
ili napunite Samsung Galaxy Note
seven phones went on board a plane now
sada je sedam telefona otišlo u avion
the Federal Aviation Administration also
Savezna uprava za avijaciju
advised against packing the phones into
savetovao sam da se telefoni ne upakuju
any checked in luggage Samsung recalled
bilo koji od prijavljenih prtljaga Samsung se prisjetio
the phone last week after reports
telefon prošle nedelje posle izveštaja
emerged of the device exploding during
se pojavio uređaj koji je eksplodirao tokom
or after charging Qantas Virgin
ili nakon punjenja Qantas Virgin
Australia have also told customers not
Australija je takođe rekla klijentima ne
to charge or use the phone during
tokom punjenja ili korišćenja telefona
flights samsung said that it would speed
letovi samsung su rekli da će ubrzati
up shipments of replacement Galaxy Note
do isporuke zamjenske Galaxy Note
seven phones to ease safety concerns
sedam telefona za ublažavanje sigurnosnih problema
Samsung has said that battery problems
Samsung je rekao da su problemi sa baterijom
were behind the phones that caught on
bili su iza telefona koji su se uhvatili
fire but that it was difficult to work
vatra, ali da je bilo teško raditi
out which phones were affected among
koji telefoni su pogođeni
those that were sold now the phone was
one koje su sada prodate telefon je bio
launched just last month and has been
pokrenut samo prošlog mjeseca i bio je
otherwise generally well received by
inače dobro prihvaćeni
consumers and critics some 2.5 million
potrošači i kritičari oko 2,5 miliona
notes Evans have been shipped globally
Evans je isporučen globalno
that's a lot Samsung has said customers
to je puno toga što je Samsung rekao korisnicima
have already who have already bought the
koji su već kupili
phone will be able to swap it for a new
telefon će ga moći zamijeniti za novi
one and that it would take about two
jedan i da će trajati oko dva
weeks to prepare replacement devices wow
tjedna za pripremu zamjenskih uređaja wow
that's a whole lot of devices that have
to je mnogo uređaja koji imaju
to go under recall jebden you just get a
ići pod podsećanje jebden te samo dobiti
new Samsung I did but it wasn't a note 7
novi Samsung sam, ali to nije bila napomena 7
okay what is it was just an s7 s
u redu šta je bilo samo s7
okay have an edge cuz you as you're
u redu, imate rubu jer ste kao vi
saying that it wasn't yours a77 yes but
rekavši da nije tvoja a77 da, ali
not the note everything seven now iphone
ne note sve sedam sada iphone
7 what is Samsung s7 it's the gemstone
7 što je Samsung s7 je dragi kamen
note 7 it's because it's the 7th
beleška 7 je zato što je sedmi
generation it's it's just like Windows
generacija je kao Windows
10 it was the 10th operating system so
To je bio 10. operativni sistem
but nobody fault oh I guess OS 10 oh is
ali niko nije kriv oh, mislim da je OS 10 oh
that how it works that's how it works
kako to funkcionira, tako funkcionira
this is how they compete we have numbers
ovako se takmiče mi imamo brojeve
it's true yeah Wow so why are yours have
Istina je, da, vau, pa zašto su tvoji
not been recalled this is specifically
to nije konkretno
just the note 7 at this point mine has
samo beleška 7 u ovom trenutku moja ima
not been recalled White has not blown up
nije opozvan Beli nije dignut u vazduh
on me good it does not overheat when
na meni dobro ne pregreva kada
it's charging we had this discussion
to je punjenje imali smo ovu diskusiju
about the the speed charging features
o mogućnostima punjenja brzine
and yes that would be my fear is like
i da bi to bio moj strah
you're pumping so much juice into this
pumpaš toliko soka u ovo
thing yeah I will say my charger gets
Da , reći ću da moj punjač dobije
hot yeah what when I when I speed
vruće yeah šta kad sam kad sam brzinu
charged the little end of the cable that
napunio je mali kraj kabla
connects to my phone that does heat up
povezuje se sa telefonom koji se zagreva
let me just remind you but yeah I know
samo da te podsetim, ali da znam
but it doesn't heat up so that it's hot
ali se ne zagreva tako da je vruće
it's just there's like a warmth to it
to je samo toplina
okay and that's the cable itself it's
ok i to je sam kabl
not the phone but it only does that when
ne telefon, već samo kada
its speed charging so obviously there is
njegova brzina punjenja je tako očigledna
some element of heat involved hmm but
neki element topline je uključen hmm ali
not enough to cause things to don't put
nije dovoljno da izazove stvari
it under your pillow while you're
dok se nalazite pod jastukom
charging it ooh do people still do that
naplaćujući ga, ljudi to i dalje rade
um I think maybe not me I've heard some
hm mislim da nisam ja sam čuo neke
stories of some teens that have had this
priče nekih tinejdžera koji su to imali
happen to them yes wow so you know what
da im se desi da znate šta
I think it is as you put on you put on
Mislim da je to kao što ste stavili
some music or whatever else you put it
neku muziku ili bilo šta drugo
under your pillow and then you lay your
ispod jastuka i onda položite
head on the pillow so that you can hear
glavu na jastuk tako da možete čuti
it without disturbing other people so
bez ometanja drugih ljudi
yeah I just use headphone use ear buds
Da, samo koristim slušalice za slušalice
yeah yeah that's what I do but I think
da, to je ono što radim, ali mislim
that's why it happens I think that's why
to je razlog zašto se to dogodi, mislim da je to zato
they end up putting it under their
oni završavaju stavljajući ih pod svoje
pillow I think it's cuz to try to sneak
jastuk Mislim da je cuz pokušati da se prikrade
around at night so parents don't see
noću tako da roditelji ne vide
it's like you cut them all in it too
to je kao da si ih sve isekao u njemu
right under the pillow yep yep where's
tačno ispod jastuka, yep yep
your phone oh no I lost it that's right
vaš telefon oh ne izgubio sam to
the pillows smoking
jastuci za pušenje
one of our sons when he was uh when he
jedan od naših sinova kada je bio uh
got his phone I should clarify when our
dobio sam telefon koji bi trebalo da pojasnim kada je naš
phones expire on her contract yet a new
telefoni ističu na njenom ugovoru, ali novi
one yeah we just give them the old phone
samo da im damo stari telefon
okay without a plan on it so they could
ok, bez plana o tome kako bi mogli
use a wife I'd home and play minecraft
koristio bih ženu kod kuće i igrao minecraft
or whatever all right but one of them he
ili bilo šta drugo osim jednog od njih
was getting up in the middle night
ustajala je sredinom noći
grabbing his phone starting to play like
Zgrabio je njegov telefon i počeo da svira
three o'clock in the morning oh but he
tri sata ujutro oh, ali on
got sneaky because once we caught him
dobio sam podli jer smo ga uhvatili
under the pillow he started putting it
pod jastukom je počeo da ga stavlja
between the pillow and the pillow cover
između jastuka i poklopca jastuka
Oh we'd lift up the pillow and is not
Oh, podigli bismo jastuk i nije
there and it's not there but I happen to
tamo i to nije tamo, ali ja sam slučajno
pick up the pillow and I'm like ooh this
pokupi jastuk i ja sam kao ovo
is heavier oh whoa he has a phone shape
je teže oh, hej on ima oblik telefona
in the case so danger he's getting
u slučaju, tako opasnost dobija
sneaky about 45 years again if I'm Jeff
Ponizno oko 45 godina opet ako sam Jeff
let's get it from definitely not me no
hajde da ga izvadimo iz definitivno ne mene
no yeah what's next surgeons have used a
ne da šta sledeći hirurzi koriste
robot to operate inside the eye and
robot za rad unutar oka i
restore sight in an absolute world first
ponovo uspostaviti vid u apsolutnom svijetu
a team at Oxford's john radcliffe
tim na Oxford's john radcliffe
hospital used the device controlled via
bolnica je koristila uređaj kontrolisan preko
joystick to remove a membrane one
džojstik za uklanjanje membrane
hundredth of a millimeter thick that's
debljina stotinke milimetra to je
small now surgeons hope that the
mali hirurzi se nadaju da će
procedure will pave the way for more
procedura će otvoriti put za više
complex aye sir how is that not complex
kompleksno, kako to nije kompleksno
as it is we're just getting started Wow
kao da smo tek počeli Wow
so anyway from work of legs I surgery
u svakom slučaju od rada na nogama sam operacija
that is currently possible with the
što je trenutno moguće sa
human hand now the patient dr. bill
ljudsku ruku sada pacijent dr. Bill
beaver is a 70 year old from Oxford and
Beaver je 70 godina star iz Oxforda i
he says he's delighted to be the first
kaže da je oduševljen što je prvi
person to undergo the robot I procedure
osoba koja će proći postupak robota I
the surgery was successful dr. beaver
operacija je bila uspješna dr. beaver
central vision in his right eye has been
centralnog vida na desnom oku je
restored good job he said the
obnovio dobar posao, rekao je
degeneration of my vision was very scary
degeneracija mog vida je bila vrlo zastrašujuća
and I was fearful I would lose my sight
i bojao sam se da ću izgubiti vid
entirely so for this intervention to
potpuno za ovu intervenciju
take place so effortlessly is a real God
odvija se tako bez napora da je pravi Bog
set I love this story totally cool i
set Volim ovu priču sasvim cool i
love it when technology is used to
volim kada je tehnologija navikla
better the life of absolutely i I think
bolji život apsolutno ja mislim
it's great I love this kind of stuff
Sjajno volim ovu vrstu stvari
when you can when you can get so precise
kada možete kada možete biti tako precizni
with something like that unreal it's
sa nečim takvim nestvarnim to je
great they can work it like nano
sjajno mogu da rade kao nano
levels yeah one one thousandth of a
nivoi da jedna hiljadita a
millimeter was a millimeter some year I
milimetar je bio milimetar neke godine
think was millimeter you said son
Mislim da si rekao milimetar sine
hundred millimeter but to think that
sto milimetara, ali da to mislim
that it is of itself was causing his
da je samo po sebi uzrok njegovog
central vision loss yeah so here you go
centralni gubitak vida, da, evo, evo
let's just put a robot in your eye and
stavimo robota u vaše oko i
fix that for you okay yeah but that's a
popravi to za tebe u redu, ali to je
small robot know it's a big robot but a
mali robot zna da je veliki robot, ali a
very precise robot it's actually like a
Veoma precizan robot je zapravo kao
like an arm so he's laying on the bed
kao ruka tako da leži na krevetu
and and this arm is coming down right
i ova ruka pada desno
but to imagine this thing coming at you
ali zamislite ovo dolazi na vas
but I mean the parts to get on it be
ali mislim na delove na koje treba naići
like needle yeah yeah like that was
kao igla yeah yeah kao da je
there on this apparatus yes yeah yeah
na ovom aparatu da da da
but still I mean the fact that you can
ali ipak mislim na činjenicu da možete
get that small just like yeah very
da dobijem malu kao i ja
precise I it's totally cool don't hook
Precizno, to je sasvim kul
it don't accidentally kick it while
to ga ne slučajno udara
you're walking by don't sneeze while
dok hodate ne kijavite
you're having that surgery yeah will not
Imaš tu operaciju da ne
bring loop to them okay now this next
dovedite petlju do njih u redu sada ovo sledeće
news story I have to say this one is for
Priča o vijestima Moram reći da je ova za
you see see see 128 DC 128 d this this
Vidite, vidite, to je 128 dc 128 d
one's for you uh-oh what do we got armed
jedan je za tebe uh-oh šta smo naoružani
drones could be used by police in the US
Droni bi mogli koristiti policija u SAD-u
state of North Dakota after local
država North Dakota nakon lokalnog
lawmakers legalized their use Oh while
zakonodavci su legalizirali svoju upotrebu Oh while
they will be limited to less than lethal
one će biti ograničene na manje od smrtonosne
weapons teargas tasers rubber bullets
oružje suzavac gume
and pepper spray could be used in theory
i biber sprej bi se mogao koristiti u teoriji
by remote controlled flying machines in
pomoću daljinski upravljanih letećih mašina u
a classic case of unintended
klasičan slučaj nenamernog
consequences the original sponsor
posljedice izvornog sponzora
Republican state representative Rick
Republikanski državni predstavnik Rick
Becker said he was unhappy with the way
Becker je rekao da je nezadovoljan načinom
that the legislation turned out his
da je zakonodavstvo ispalo njegovo
original intention was to prevent law
prvobitna namjera bila je spriječiti zakon
enforcement officials from using the
službenici za sprovođenje zakona
unmanned aerial vehicles from conducting
bespilotne letjelice od vođenja
surveillance on private property without
bez nadzora nad privatnom imovinom
a warrant wow talk about a change he
nalog za razgovor o promeni
says in my opinion there should be a
kaže da bi trebalo da postoji
nice red line drones should not be
Dronovi lijepe crvene linije ne bi trebali biti
weaponized he said the original draft of
rekao je originalni nacrt
the House bill 1328 said a state agency
račun zakona 1328 kaže da je državna agencija
may not authorize the use of including
ne može odobriti upotrebu uključujući
granting a permit
davanje dozvole
permit to use an unmanned aircraft armed
dozvolu za upotrebu bespilotne letelice naoružane
with any lethal or non-lethal weapons
sa bilo kojim smrtonosnim ili nesmrtonosnim oružjem
including firearms pepper spray beanbag
uključujući i vatreno oružje papar sprej beanbag
guns maize and sound based weapons
oružje kukuruza i oružja
however the state's police union amended
međutim, državni policijski sindikat je izmijenjen
the bill limiting the band to only
račun za ograničavanje bend samo
lethal weapons meaning that sounds can
smrtonosno oružje što znači da zvuči mogu
sound cannons rubber bullets could be
zvučni topovi mogu biti gumeni metci
used on police drones it's unclear
na policijskim trutovima je nejasno
whether local police departments will
hoće li lokalne policijske uprave
use weaponized drones even though
iako koriste bespilotne bespilotne letelice
they're technically legal Wow so for the
oni su tehnički pravni Wow tako za
last couple of weeks you can half of
poslednjih par nedelja možeš pola
this discussion back and forth with c128
ovu diskusiju sa c128
d about i think it's an argument but i
Mislim da je to argument, ali ja
think he just won yeah at this point
mislim da je upravo pobedio u ovom trenutku
North Dakota just sealed the deal on oh
Severna Dakota je zapečatila ugovor
my gosh how does this happen isn't this
Bože, kako se ovo događa nije ovo
bureaucracy at its best we're okay here
birokratija u najboljem slučaju smo ovde dobro
here we go I'm gonna say drones cannot
evo idemo reći da dronovi ne mogu
be used by police to have weapons and
policija koristi oružje i
blah blah blah and then they all sit
blah blah blah i onda svi sjede
around the table say oh that's a great
oko stola kažu da je to super
idea let's do that yeah let's put
Ideja hajde da to uradimo
weapons on drones so I think it's like
oružje na trutovima, tako da mislim da je to
all this red tape gets all mixed up and
sva ova birokratija postaje sve pomešana i
I just come on now you know okay so
Samo dođite sada , dobro znate
there's a meme that I've used a couple
tu je mem koji sam koristio par
times it's a Picard and Riker doing the
Pikard i Riker rade
double facepalm is classic mean with
dvostruki facepalm je klasično značenje sa
this story I feel like one facepalm
Ovu priču osećam kao jedan obraz
doesn't cut it you need a double
ne odseci je treba ti duplo
facepalm c128 d just won the Internet
facepalm c128 d upravo je osvojio internet
big thanks this week to write a few Nash
Velika hvala ove nedelje da napišem nekoliko Naša
in our community viewers for submitting
u našoj zajednici gledaoci za slanje
stories to us if you found a new story
priče za nas ako ste pronašli novu priču
you'd like to send email into newsroom a
želite poslati e-poštu u redakciju a
category 5 TV for all your tech news
kategorija 5 TV za sve vaše tehnološke vijesti
with a slight linux bias visit category
sa blagom linux bias posjetom kategoriji
five dot TV news room at newsroom
pet tačaka TV vijesti u redakciji
category five TV for the category five
pet kategorija TV za petu kategoriju
TV news room i'm jeff
Soba za TV vijesti Ja sam Jeff
worcester
worcester